Guide to the Judy Blume Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 2017 Acquisition, 1952-2017; 117.75; (125 boxes) + 1 roll
  - Key West Material, 1961-2015; 99.62; (106 boxes)
    - "JB notes to all esp. writers interviewed prob. with L.Street script", 1991, undated (Box 24)
    - "Faxes to Longstreet + Nelle", 1990–1991 (Box 24)
    - Just as long as we're together, screenplay, 1991, undated; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Just as long as we're together, notes related to project, 1989-1991, undated (Box 24)
    - "Feb 10, 1991 draft sent to Longstreet", 1991 February 10 (Box 24)
    - "Notes + outlines Hilma and JB Monday, April 1-Friday, April 5, 1991", 1991, undated (Box 24)
    - "JB + HW next to last draft Apr. 19 + 24 1991", 1991 April (Box 24)
    - "Jan 21, 1991 JB notes on Longstreet draft", 1991 January 21 (Box 24)
    - "JB + HW April 25, 1991", 1991 April 25 (Box 24)
    - "Pitch/to network notes", 1989-1990, undated (Box 24)
    - "JB + HW work in progress April 1991", 1991, undated; 4 folders (Box 24)
    - Fan mail, 1988-1989, undated (Box 25)
    - "Correspondence 1982-1988 agents-American", 1981-1987, undated (Box 25)
    - Letters to Judy, "FM/Kids 1989", 1988-1989, undated (Box 25)
    - Correspondence - Hughe Massie Limited, 1978-1989, undated (Box 25)
    - Fan mail, 1988-1989, undated (Box 25)
    - "Correspondence - articles/interviews - 1989-1990", 1988–1990 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence - authors, 1987-1990, undated (Box 25)
    - "Correspondence: authors/Norma Klein 1979-1989", 1979-1989, undated (Box 25)
    - "Correspondence, editors 1986-1990", 1986-1990, undated (Box 25)
    - "Correspondence, editors, British 1986-1990", 1986-1990, undated (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1984, undated (Box 25)
    - Professional correspondence, 1987-1990, undated (Box 25)
    - "Correspondence: publishers, foregin (other than Britain) 1988" (Box 25)
    - "Correspondence/requests: auctions 1990", 1990-1991, undated (Box 25)
    - "Auctions, schools 1990" (Box 26)
    - "Correspondence: requests/book quotes 1988-1990" (Box 26)
    - "Routine requests 1990", 1990–1991 (Box 26)
    - "Speaking engagements 1990" (Box 26)
    - "Corresp/requests 1987-1990 writing/manuscripts (advice, etc)" (Box 26)
    - "Correspondence/subrights LA Times column 1984-" (Box 26)
    - "Correspondence: TV related 1984-1985", 1978-1985, undated (Box 26)
    - "'Decade of Literary Lions,' New York Library, Nov. 8, 1990", 1990, undated (Box 26)
    - "Speaking engagement: acceptance Poets & Writers literary dinner - December 6,1990", 1990, undated (Box 26)
    - "Correspondence/requests: routine 1990", 1989-1990, undated (Box 26)
    - Correspondence/articles about Judy Blume, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Correspondence/British publishers, 1969-1983, undated (Box 26)
    - Correspondence from schools, 1983-1984, undated (Box 26)
    - "Corresp/personal - through 1983", 1981-1983, undated (Box 26)
    - "Corresp/requests/auctions - 1984 (+2 Oct. - 1983)", 1983-1985, undated (Box 26)
    - "Correspondence-1984-Jan/Feb/March routine invitations" (Box 26)
    - "Correspondence - 1984 - Apr/Dec 1984 routine invitations" (Box 26)
    - "Correspondence: 1984 routine requests", 1983–1985 (Box 26)
    - "Awards: through 1982", 1980-1984, undated (Box 26)
    - Superfudge, Tiger eyes, "Awards - Young Readers Medal - Nov. 83 San Diego", 1983 (Box 26)
    - "School groups - 1983-1984 school year" (Box 26)
    - "School groups - 1980-1983", undated (Box 26)
    - "Awards: 1983-", 1981–1984 (Box 27)
    - "School groups-1983-1984 school yr (accompanying ltrs fr teachers etc.)", 1983-1984, undated (Box 27)
    - "February Chorus [?] 1988", 1985 (Box 27)
    - "January 1985", 1984–1985 (Box 27)
    - "Foster parents plan", 1981–1985 (Box 27)
    - "Contractor deals", 1990-1991, undated (Box 27)
    - "Correspondence personal 1992", 1990-1992, undated (Box 27)
    - "Personal correspondence - 1992", 1991–1992 (Box 27)
    - "Correspondence: personal 1991", 1983-1992, undated (Box 27)
    - "Correspondeonce: business not career related: before 83", 1981 (Box 27)
    - "Correspondence: professional, related to Judy's work (before 1983)", 1981–1983 (Box 27)
    - "Correspondence: personal (before 1980)", 1977–1979 (Box 27)
    - "Routine requests - 1983" (Box 27)
    - "Corr: - routine invitations 1[9]83" (Box 27)
    - "Correspondence/editors-British", 1984–1985 (Box 27)
    - Professional correspondence, 1983–1984; 2 folders (Box 27)
    - "Corresp/requests - speaking engagements 1985", 1984–1986 (Box 27)
    - "Corresp/requests - routine 1985", 1984–1985 (Box 27)
    - "Bar Harbor Bank (1989)" (Box 28)
    - Financial records, 1982-1989, undated; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - "Fidelity Keogh Plan (open)", 1981-1987, undated (Box 28)
    - Forever, "serial reprints", 1985 (Box 28)
    - Financial records, 1980-1984, undated (Box 28)
    - "Topsy Turvy Productions, Inc. formal papers", 1987-1988, undated (Box 28)
    - Smart women, "Pub. tours/ PKTBKS Sales Confer. December 1984", 1984 December (Box 28)
    - Smart women Tour - US, 1983-1984, undated (Box 28)
    - Smart women, "Publicity tour - England/Scotland May 1984", 1984, undated (Box 28)
    - Smart women, "British Tour - Spring 1984", undated (Box 28)
    - Letters to Judy tour, 1986, undated (Box 28)
    - G.P. Putnam interview, undated (Box 28)
    - Letters to Judy ,"Publicity tour", 1986 (Box 28)
    - Smart women, promotional material, 1984-1985, undated (Box 28)
    - Smart women, "Publictiy tours - 1978-1981 (information, expenses, etc.)", 1978-1981, undated (Box 28)
    - Smart women, "Publicity/promotion British", 1985 (Box 28)
    - Smart women, "Pub. tours/SW-PKTBKS-corresp. misc.", 1984–1985 (Box 28)
    - "The last tour", undated (Box 28)
    - Smart women, tour, 1985, undated (Box 28)
    - Smart women, press release, undated (Box 28)
    - "Putnam publishing tour - 1986", 1986, undated (Box 28)
    - "Publicity tour, England 1986 Letters to Judy ", 1986, undated (Box 28)
    - "Publicity tour: Pocketbooks Letters to Judy, March 1987", 1987, undated (Box 28)
    - "Publicity tour: Just as long as we're together /Orchard/1987", 1987 January 29 (Box 28)
    - "Receipts, letters tour/UK", 1986, undated (Box 28)
    - "Correspondence: requests, routine Jan 1989" (Box 28)
    - "Correspondence/requests: auctions 1989", 1988–1989 (Box 29)
    - "Correspondence/requests: school auctions 1988-1989" (Box 29)
    - "Speaking engagements-acceptance New York Library Association Buffalo, October 1988" (Box 29)
    - "Speaking engagements: acceptance "Ready to go" WNEW-TV, Boston September 7, 1989" (Box 29)
    - "Correspondence: Requests, speaking engagements 1989" (Box 29)
    - "Calle Sierpe sale", 1978–1985 (Box 29)
    - "Wynne lawsuit", 1985 (Box 29)
    - "David Wynne lawsuit (3/85) (Calle Sierpe sale)", 1985–1988 (Box 29)
    - "David Wynne", 1984–1985 (Box 29)
    - "Creative coalition", 1997-1998, undated (Box 29)
    - "Teen Ink", 2000 (Box 29)
    - Awards from schools, 1979-1981, undated (Box 29)
    - "Awards 1985", 1984–1986 (Box 29)
    - "Censorship: articles and related materials (open) '81-83", 1981-1982, undated (Box 29)
    - "Censorship: correspondence/children 1980-1983", 1980-1983, undated (Box 29)
    - "Censorship: correspondence-children 1984-1985", 1983–1985 (Box 29)
    - "Censorship: correspondence-adults 1979-1983" (Box 29)
    - "Censorship: correspondence-adults 1984-1985" (Box 29)
    - Censorship articles, 1985, undated (Box 29)
    - "Censorship: news clippings and related (open) '81-83", 1980-1982, undated (Box 29)
    - "Correspondence/requests 1984-87 writing/manuscripts (advice, etc.)", 1980–1987 (Box 30)
    - "Correspon/sub rights '82-85", 1981–1984 (Box 30)
    - "Endorsements", 1983 May 19 (Box 30)
    - "Old deeds", 1976–1978 (Box 30)
    - " Letters to Judy: Marian Rees", 1987 (Box 30)
    - Correspondence from children/teenagers, 1986-1987, undated (Box 30)
    - "Seattle Childrens Theatre script draft", 1986, undated (Box 30)
    - "Marian Rees/JB", 1987, undated (Box 30)
    - "Correspondence/articles/interviews 1984-1987" (Box 30)
    - "Seattle Childrens Theater script/revised by JB and other items", 1987 (Box 30)
    - "Corresp/request/auctions-1985" (Box 30)
    - "Correspodence: auctions 1986" (Box 30)
    - "Correspondence/requests 1987 auctions" (Box 30)
    - "Corresp/requests/schl. auctions1984/1985 school year" (Box 30)
    - "School auctions (1985-1986) school year (Box 30)
    - "Corr/school auctions 1986-1987 school year" (Box 30)
    - Manuscripts sent to Judy Blume, 1984–1985 (Box 31)
    - "Correspondence: book quotes 1986-1987" (Box 31)
    - "School groups 1986-1987 with teacher letter, etc." (Box 31)
    - "Projects/individual students", 1983–1986 (Box 31)
    - "Schools - re: author projects with reponses to teachers & students", 1983–1987 (Box 31)
    - "Kids really want to know", undated (Box 31)
    - "School letters 1986-87 many envelopes", 1986–1987 (Box 31)
    - "School letters groups in one envelope", 1985 (Box 31)
    - "School groups (one env) 1984-1985 school year" (Box 31)
    - "School groups (individuals) 1984-1985 school year" (Box 31)
    - "School groups 1985-1986 with teacher letter, etc." (Box 31)
    - "School groups 1985-86 one envelope", 1985-1986, undated (Box 31)
    - "Correspondence/requests 1986 routine, various, Jan-Jun", 1985–1986 (Box 31)
    - "Corresp/requests routine/various 1986" (Box 31)
    - Note for filing system, undated (Box 32)
    - "Corres: editors and publishers US-through 1997", 1995-1996, undated (Box 32)
    - "Correspondence: editors U.K. 1997", 1995-1998, undated (Box 32)
    - "Personal correspondence 1996", 1996, undated (Box 32)
    - "Corres: editors foreign (thru 1997)", 1991-1998, undated (Box 32)
    - "Personal corerspondence 1995", 1994–1995 (Box 32)
    - "Corres: professional 1991-1997", 1994–1998 (Box 32)
    - High school reunion ephemera, 1996 (Box 32)
    - "Correspondence: personal 1997", 1995-1997, undated (Box 32)
    - "Corres: personal 97-98", 1997-1998, undated (Box 32)
    - "Corres: authors: to 1997", 1993-1997, undated (Box 32)
    - "White House correspondence", 1993 (Box 32)
    - "Censorship corres: Forever ", 1981–1997 (Box 32)
    - "Censorship corres: ALA", 1986–1991 (Box 32)
    - "Censorship articles/materials 1986-", 1976-1990, undated (Box 32)
    - "Censorship articles JB books", 1985-1990, undated (Box 32)
    - "'X-Rated books' - pamphlet", undated (Box 32)
    - "Censorship information 1994" (Box 32)
    - "Censorship - ACLU", 1993-1994, undated (Box 32)
    - Blubber, Deenie, Tiger eyes, Are you there God? It's me, Margaret "Censorship - Norman, OK", 1993 December 7 (Box 32)
    - "Censorship - Forever Rib Lake, Wisconsin, 1993-1996, undated (Box 32)
    - "Censorship corres: NCAC 522", 1984–1999 (Box 32)
    - "Correspondence: editors U.K. 1991", 1991, undated (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: editors U.K. 1992", 1992, undated (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: brochure material - U.K.", 1990-1991, undated (Box 33)
    - Correspondence: brochure material - U.S.", 1987-1991, undated (Box 33)
    - "Awards - 1991-1992" (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: editors U.K. 1989-90", 1989-1990, undated (Box 33)
    - Personal correspondence, 1993, undated (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: editors US 1991-92", 1983–1992 (Box 33)
    - Correspondence regarding royalties, 1988–1992 (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: requests book quotes - 1991-92 regrets", 1991–1992 (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: requests interviews - 1988-92 acceptance", 1990–1992 (Box 33)
    - "Correspodence: articles/interviews/regrets", 1991 (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: requests JB to write - 1990-92 regrets", 1991–1992 (Box 33)
    - "Routine requests - 1990-92", 1991–1992 (Box 33)
    - Correspondence, The Author's Guild, 1992 (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: requests pers. appearance - 1990-92 regrets", 1991–1992 (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: personal appearance - 1991-92 acceptance", 1991–1992 (Box 33)
    - "Speaking engagements/acceptance: Nat. Council of Teachers of Engl Seattle, Nov. 22-24, 1991", 1991 November (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: TV/movie", 1987–1991 (Box 33)
    - "Correspondence: speaking engagements 1991-1992 regrets" (Box 33)
    - "Holiday greetings 1993", 1993, undated (Box 33)
    - "San Acacio lot", 1984–1992 (Box 34)
    - "Equinox Health Club", 1993, undated (Box 34)
    - "Kids fund - projects for 1988 possible funding (unsolicited)", 1987–1988 (Box 34)
    - "KF - contributions", 1983 (Box 34)
    - "Kids fund - 1991 final report", 1991 June 30 (Box 34)
    - "Kids fund - charitable contributions - 1991" (Box 34)
    - "KF - correspondence 1991", 1991, undated (Box 34)
    - "Kids fund", 1989, undated (Box 34)
    - "Kids fund correspondence 1992/93", 1992 September (Box 34)
    - "KF - projects for possible funding 1989", 1989–1991 (Box 34)
    - "Kids fund - miscellaneous", 1984, undated (Box 34)
    - "Kids fund - mailing list old pre-1985", 1984–1985 (Box 34)
    - "KF - mailing list, pre-1985", 1983-1985, undated (Box 34)
    - "KF - mailing lists 1987" (Box 34)
    - "KF funding ideas 1990", 1986-1990, undated (Box 34)
    - "KF - expenses/invoices, etc.", 1985 (Box 34)
    - "KF tax and legal pre-1985", 1982–1983 (Box 34)
    - Kids fund correspondence, 1985–1987 (Box 34)
    - "Royalties / British", 1986–1989 (Box 34)
    - "Correspondence: personal 1986", 1986, undated (Box 34)
    - "Correspondence, personal: 1987", 1987-1995, undated (Box 34)
    - "Correspondence: professional 1986" (Box 35)
    - "Correspondence: professional 1987", 1987, undated (Box 35)
    - "Correspondence, routine 1987 Jan - June", 1987, undated (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, routine 1987 July - December" (Box 35)
    - "Correspondence, speaking 1986 Jan - June" (Box 35)
    - "Corresp/requests 1986 speaking engagements" (Box 35)
    - "Acceptances/speaking engagements Amer. Psych. Assn - May 20-24, 1985 Dallas, Texas", 1984–1985 (Box 35)
    - "Acceptances/speaking engagements Chicago Pub. Library - Nov. 17, 1984 Literary Arts Ball" (Box 35)
    - "Acceptances/speaking engagements Burger King - October 1, 1984 Reno, Nevada" (Box 35)
    - Correspondence: speaking engagements, 1986, undated (Box 35)
    - "New York Public Library October 31, 1986" (Box 35)
    - "Speaking engagements/acceptances Westport Public Library, Sept. 1986" (Box 35)
    - Correspondence: Westport Country Playhouse, 1986 September 24 (Box 35)
    - "Speaking engagements/acceptances ACLU of Georgia, December 1986", 1986, undated (Box 35)
    - "Speaking engagements/acceptances Center for Population Options Los Angeles, Dec. 1986", 1986, undated (Box 35)
    - "Correspondence, speaking 1987 July - December" (Box 35)
    - "ABA meetings, Washington D.C. May 1987" (Box 35)
    - "Correspondence, speaking 1987 Jan - June" (Box 35)
    - "Speaking engagements - acceptances Inst. for Mental Health Initiative 5/20/87", 1987, undated (Box 35)
    - "Speaking engagements - acceptances Kean College, June 1987", 1987, undated (Box 35)
    - "Speaking engagements - acceptances Concord, New Hampshire, June 1987", 1987, undated (Box 35)
    - "Speaking engagements - acceptances NY Public Library, 11/11/87", 1987 (Box 35)
    - "Speech - Author's Guild Monday, November 8", 1993 (Box 36)
    - " Catcher in the rye Excerpt - NCAC", 1994 (Box 36)
    - "NCAC party for the First Amendment", 1993–1994 (Box 36)
    - "NCAC - benefit - '94", 1993-1994, undated (Box 36)
    - "NCAC - fundraiser 1995", 1995, undated (Box 36)
    - NCAC books in trouble, 1996 (Box 36)
    - "JB thank you notes NCAC fundraiser", 1995-1996, undated (Box 36)
    - "Censorship: Educational Paperwork Assn. 1/87", 1987 January (Box 36)
    - "NCAC - general information", 1992-1993, undated (Box 36)
    - "Censorship: Peoria (1984)", 1984-1985, undated (Box 36)
    - "Podesta - TV violence", 1993 (Box 36)
    - "NCAC - censorship meeting sex panic", 1986-1993, undated (Box 36)
    - "NCAC - Working Group [on Women, Censorship and "Pornography]", 1992-1993, undated (Box 36)
    - "Trump club fiasco 3/90", 1990, undated (Box 36)
    - Resources about teenagers and alcohol, undated (Box 36)
    - "Resources: child abuse", 1988, undated (Box 36)
    - "Resources: depression", undated (Box 36)
    - "Resources eating disorders", 1989 November 9 (Box 36)
    - "Resources: incest/sexual abuse", 1990, undated (Box 36)
    - "Resources/masturbation", 1995, undated (Box 36)
    - "Resources/sexual fantasies", undated (Box 36)
    - "Resources sick & disabled", 1989 November 9 (Box 36)
    - "Resources: trouble in school", 1993, undated (Box 36)
    - "Censorship - Feminists for Free Expression", 1993, undated (Box 36)
    - "Censorship - Forever Moscow, IA", 1995-1996, undated (Box 36)
    - "Censorship - Herb Forstal", 1993, undated (Box 36)
    - "Censorship - Enough is enough", 1993-1994, undated (Box 36)
    - "Special letters 1984 (adults)", 1984–1985 (Box 37)
    - General correspondence, 1984–1985 (Box 37)
    - "Special letters 1985 (adults)" (Box 37)
    - "Fan Mail: special/adults 1986" (Box 37)
    - "Fan Mail: Adults 1987" (Box 37)
    - "FM/ Letters to Judy /Adults 1986" (Box 37)
    - "FM/ Letters to Judy /Adults 1987", 1986–1987 (Box 37)
    - "Special letters 1983 (Sept - Dec)" (Box 37)
    - "Special Letters 1983 Originals (Sept/Dec)" (Box 37)
    - "Special letters 1984 children (originals)", 1981–1984 (Box 37)
    - "Fan mail - special - children 1985" (Box 37)
    - "FM/kids 1986" (Box 37)
    - "FM/letters/kids '86", 1986 (Box 37)
    - "FM/ Letters to Judy /kids 1986" (Box 37)
    - Smart women, 1984 (Box 37)
    - "Fan mail: Wifey ", 1979, undated (Box 37)
    - "FM/special/children 1986" (Box 37)
    - "Fan mail: kids 1987" (Box 38)
    - "FM/ Letters to Judy /kids 1987 Jan 1-June 30", 1987, undated (Box 38)
    - "FM/ Letters to Judy /kids 1987 July 1-Dec. 31", 1987–1988 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous work by children, undated (Box 38)
    - Magazines, 1973–1984 (Box 38)
    - Magazines, 1978 December 3 (Box 39)
    - Scrapbooks from students, 1987; 3 folders (Box 38)
    - Scrapbook of clippings, circa 1960-1974 (Box 43)
    - "When someone you love dies", 1978-1979, undated (Box 40)
    - "Censorship", undated (Box 40)
    - "From Australia", 1978–1982 (Box 40)
    - "From other lands", 1982–1983 (Box 40)
    - "Foreign: Australia:, 1982-1983, undated (Box 40)
    - "Foreign: England", 1982-1985, undated (Box 40)
    - "Special fan letters for special box", 1980–1983 (Box 40)
    - "Adult fans", 1984, undated (Box 40)
    - "Fan mail/before 1979", 1976-1978, undated (Box 40)
    - " Forever …from parents, teachers, and kids", 1982-1983, undated (Box 40)
    - "Negative letters: excluding Forever ", 1982–1983 (Box 40)
    - "Special letters. Sept 83-84 young people", 1983, undated (Box 40)
    - "Adult fans", 1980-1982, undated (Box 40)
    - "Adults…positive ideas and comments", 1979–1982 (Box 40)
    - "From teachers", 1980 (Box 40)
    - "Judy's copies letters", 1980-1983, undated (Box 40)
    - Miscellaneous letters, undated (Box 40)
    - "Negative letters - 1982-1983", 1977–1980 (Box 40)
    - "Fan mail ", 1976-1978, undated (Box 40)
    - "To be filed", 1976-1982, undated (Box 40)
    - "Recent fan mail B", 1982-1983, undated (Box 40)
    - " Tiger eyes and Death", 1982–1983 (Box 40)
    - Wifey, 1978–1983 (Box 40)
    - "Thank you's", 1976-1983, undated (Box 40)
    - Miscellaneous corerspondence, 1978-1983, undated; 3 folders (Box 40)
    - "Sept. 26 letters to file on Dear Judy", 1985, undated (Box 41)
    - "Letters of Ellen Bright", 1983, undated (Box 41)
    - "Parent-child sharing books", 1978-1981, undated (Box 41)
    - "Negative letters 1982-1983 various", 1978-1982, undated (Box 41)
    - Are you there God? It's me, Margaret ,"relating to bras, periods, being normal", 1981-1983, undated (Box 41)
    - "Handicapped", 1983, undated (Box 41)
    - "Fudgie - etc.", 1983 (Box 41)
    - "Friends - popularity - moving", 1983 (Box 41)
    - "Editorial responses", 1975–1976 (Box 41)
    - "Divorce", 1979, undated (Box 41)
    - "Books (stores, libraries, by age groups)", 1979–1981 (Box 41)
    - "Excerpts - typed", 1978 (Box 41)
    - " Blubber - Neg & pos., adults &kids", 1978-1983, undated (Box 41)
    - " Deanie all categories", 1977-1980, undated (Box 41)
    - "Censorship", 1980–1983 (Box 41)
    - " Forever letters neg, various categories", 1976–1983 (Box 41)
    - " Forever /positive", 1977–1983 (Box 41)
    - "Fain mail - special - Ellen Bright", 1986-1995, undated; 6 folders (Box 41)
    - "Sarah Day", 1987-1998, undated; 4 folders (Box 41)
    - "Sarah Day", 1987-1998, undated; 2 folders (Box 42)
    - "Jason Edwards", 1991-1999, undated; 3 folders (Box 42)
    - "Correspondence: Tom Bernagozzi", 1990–1999 (Box 42)
    - "Josianne Gregoire", 1991–1998 (Box 42)
    - "Correspondence/Halperin Family", 1990, undated (Box 42)
    - "Here's to You, Judy Blume by Nicole McDermott", 1998 November 24 (Box 42)
    - "Writing statements/Tips by JB corres-pre", 1979-1980, undated (Box 42)
    - "I'll be Watching You by Sarah Marie Day", 1997 August 25 (Box 42)
    - Writings and correspondence from Tom Bernagozzi's third grade class", 1988 (Box 42)
    - Books created for Judy Blume by school children, 1988-1990, undated; 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Books created for Judy Blume by school children, 1990 April 3 (Box 39)
    - "Correspondence/Fans: Kim Rydgig", 1987-1990, undated; 5 folders (Box 42)
    - "Correspondence/Fans: Kim Rydgig", 1988-1991, undated; 10 folders (Box 44)
    - Card files, undated (Box 45)
    - Card files, undated (Box 46)
    - "Interviews/articles", 1998-2008, undated; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - "JB interviews/articles", 1991-2005, undated (Box 47)
    - " Double Fudge reviews/articles", 2002-2003, undated (Box 47)
    - "Miriam Richter Vassar dissertation", 1998 (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and articles, 2004-2006, undated (Box 47)
    - Magazines, 1998–2007; 3 folders (Box 47)
    - Magazines, 1999–2009; 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Otherwise known as Sheila the great, material related to film production, 1988, undated (Box 48)
    - Magazines, 2002, undated (Box 48)
    - "Misc. correspondence '97-'98", 1997-2000, undated; 4 folders (Box 48)
    - "Corres: personal/pending", 1998, undated (Box 48)
    - "N.Y. correspondence - other", 1998-1999, undated (Box 48)
    - "Indianapolis - May 7th", 1998–1999 (Box 48)
    - "Millenium Committee", 1997–1998 (Box 48)
    - "Corres: professional - to file", 1998, undated (Box 48)
    - "MS. Foundation Jennifer Baumgardner", 1997–1998 (Box 48)
    - "Web responses in progress", 1998 (Box 48)
    - Summer sisters, ephemera, undated (Box 48)
    - "Judy personal", 1998, undated (Box 48)
    - "Corresp: fans - 1998 - special e-mail" (Box 49)
    - "Corres: Special fan pre-1999 Censorship", 1986-1999, undated (Box 49)
    - "Donations - $ - sent 99/00", 1999–2000 (Box 49)
    - "Corres: Special fans 1998- (includes e-mail)", 1998–1999 (Box 49)
    - "Corres: Professional 1998", 1997-1998, undated; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - "Regrets - done- 200", 2000 (Box 49)
    - "Regrets 2001", 2000–2001 (Box 49)
    - "Auctions: acknowledged", 1998-2000, undated (Box 49)
    - "Randy's book promo", 1999, undated (Box 49)
    - "Book tours - Summer sisters - 1998 publicity & reviews Double Fudge - 2002", 1998–2002 (Box 49)
    - " Double Fudge tour - Eticket receipts", 2002 (Box 49)
    - Summer sisters, miscellaneous material, 1998-2003, undated; 5 folders (Box 49)
    - Otherwise known as Sheila the great, "one act musical", 2000; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - In the unlikley event, "real first draft Spring 2011" (Box 50)
    - In the unlikley event, draft, undated; 3 folders (Box 50)
    - In the unlikely event, working revision, 2014 October (Box 50)